Hi Vogue, I'm Hailey Bieber, and this is what's in my bag.
So, first things first, this is my hand cream that I have with me at all times, you know, just for when my hands are feeling a little
bit dry.
So that's my hand cream.
Um, next thing is, this is my sleeping mask that I wear when I'm sleeping.
Just, you know, like...
Ah.
This is my favorite perfume.
I've basically been wearing this my entire life.
I'm obsessed with it.
Smells really vanilla.
It's really gorgeous.
It really does all the work for you without you having to do anything.
Very effortless.
These are just a couple of books that I've been reading.
I love this one.
Probably my fourth or fifth time reading it.
So good.
Another one that I've been loving recently.
This is actually my second copy of it.
Yeah.
I've been taking a lot of notes from this one.
This, of course, is my road lip treatment.
Obsessed with this.
Take it with me everywhere.
I always keep a couple on me.
Oh, one more.
Just keep those there.
This is my journal.
This is where I put all my thoughts, all of my ideas go into this.
I couldn't go anywhere without it.
I feel like my whole life is in here.
It's precious to me.
This is a little bear keychain I've had since I was a teenager.
And this is a little pocket mirror that I keep with me for touch-ups and what have you.
This is my phone.
Very straightforward, obviously.
These are a couple more that I keep on me.
And I really just use them for a lot of the simple stuff, like surfing anonymously, commenting, stalking, viewing girls'
pages, making multiple accounts.
You know, that kind of thing.
People ask me about my skincare routine all the time, and I'm very open about it.
I talk about all the things I use, all of the treatments I've tried.
And I'm usually not a gatekeeper, but I have been gatekeeping this one because it's really, really special to me.
But I'm going to share it today.
Basically, this is a really rare and special face mask that you can only get if you get on a sailboat and sail to the Bermuda Triangle.
Once you get there, you have to track down the incredibly rare sunfish, and you have to harvest their eggs, but you can only harvest one in a
thousand because those specific eggs have the correct DNA to make this mask.
So it's very special to me, but does wonders, wonders for the skin.
Anyways, this is my scrunchie that, obviously, I keep with me at all times.
I like to put it on my wrist sometimes.
And oh, here's another lip treatment.
Add it to the pile.
What is this doing in here?
Delicious.
This is my Hayley Bieber smoothie.
I have one every single day.
I would say it's probably 90% of the reason why my skin looks the way it does.
I read online that videos with small
animals get a lot more likes and comments.
So this is Bonnie.
Bonnie's gonna be joining me today.
And I really do like to have just a little companion with me at all times, typically in my bag with me.
But in all seriousness, if you are looking to adopt, Pups Without Borders is a great place to check out.
Woo, Bonnie, you're a good girl!
Okay, so last but not least, this is a little tincture potion that I got.
I would say probably when I was around 12, my dad flew me to go meet with this witch who lived in the mountains.
And she made this specifically for me.
She told me that it would make a young Canadian pop star fall in love with me.
So, yeah, I've been taking this one for years.
Absolutely love it.
And um, yeah, thanks dad.
Bonnie, I have to do the outro with you here.
So that's everything that was in my bag.
Thank you so much for watching.
I hope you guys learned a lot about me watching this video.
Thank you, Vogue.
I appreciate you guys.
Love you guys.
And thank you to Bonnie.
Do do do there, do do do do.
Woo!